<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
	<name>Simple Recycling</name>
	<author>Lanilor, Proxyer, Arvkus</author>
	<packageId>lanilor.simplerecycling</packageId>
	<steamAppId IgnoreIfNoMatchingField="True">2079862064</steamAppId>
	<url>https://github.com/Arvkus/Simple-recycling</url>
	<supportedVersions>
		<li>1.5</li>
	</supportedVersions>
	<modVersion IgnoreIfNoMatchingField="True">2.0.0</modVersion>
	<loadBefore>
		<li>Proxyer.JPT.rimsenalJP</li>
	</loadBefore>
	<loadAfter>
		<li>brrainz.harmony</li>
		<li>ludeon.rimworld</li>
		<li>ludeon.rimworld.royalty</li>
		<li>ludeon.rimworld.ideology</li>
		<li>unlimitedhugs.hugslib</li>
		<li>OskarPotocki.VanillaFactionsExpanded.Core</li>
		<li>OskarPotocki.VanillaFactionsExpanded.MedievalModule</li>
		<li>vindar.medievaltimes</li>
		<li>notfood.MendAndRecycle</li>
	</loadAfter>
	<description><![CDATA[
<color=#5AA9D6><size=17><b>IMPORTANT</b></size></color>
This mod is an updated version of "Simple Recycling" made by Lanilor to 1.0. All rights to this mod are with Lanilor and I am responsible for all issues that arise with this 1.1-1.5 version. If you have any problems, please report them on this mod's workshop page.

<size=20>Special measures for v1.5.x :</size>
In RimWorld v1.5, Smelting is now limited to metal. For this reason, it is no longer possible to recycle clothing into the materials it was made from with xml files prior to v1.4.

For this reason, I took special measures for v1.5. Added a patch that forces all non-metal craftable apparel added in Core and 3 types of DLC to be recycled into cloth. All tribal apparel (tribalwear and veils) will be plainleather.

<color=#5AA9D6><size=17>Description</size> :</color>
v1.5.0
<size=20>Simple Recyclning</size>

A simple mod that adds recycling of apparel in the same way weapons are smeltable in the core version.

- Added recycle apparel bill to Crafting Spot (only "Lost Tribe" start).
  No need resarch, but work speed was slow. Supports the neolithic tech age.

To recycle apparel, research "apparel recycling" and then add the bill to a tailoring workbench.

<color=#5AA9D6><size=17>Compatibility</size> :</color>
for RimWorld 1.3-1.4.
Added processing and patches to fix problems that could not be researched due to the industrial tech level of mods in the medieval ages. Currently, it is possible to recycle apparels with the following medieval mods.

Medieval Times Unofficial Update (1.4)
Vanilla Factions Expanded - Medieval
MendAndRecycle
Micro Designations

Medieval Overhaul (1.4)

If you have "Micro Designations" enabled in your mod list, clicking on the item you want to recycle in-game will reveal a corresponding "recycle at workbench" button.
This is available for both Tribal Start and Normal Start.

I would like to thank <b>g0ldheart_rr</b> and <b>pgames-food</b> for suggesting this idea.


<color=#5AA9D6><size=17>Translation</size> :</color>
English, Japanese


Original mod : Simple Recycling ; RimWorld 1.0 version Original
Original Mod author : Lanilor
Steam Workshop Link : 
https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1419006111
https://github.com/Lanilor/

 ]]></description>
</ModMetaData>